(slow rock music)
♪ Another head hangs lowly ♪
♪ Child is slowly taken ♪
♪ And the violence,
caused such silence ♪
♪ Who are we mistaken ♪
♪ But you see, it's not me ♪
♪ It's not my family ♪
♪ In your head, in your head,
they are fighting ♪
♪ With their tanks,
and their bombs ♪
♪ And their bombs,
and their guns ♪
♪ In your head, in your head
they are crying ♪
♪ In your head, in your head ♪
♪ Zombie, zombie, zombie-ie-ie ♪
♪ What's in your head,
in your head ♪
♪ Zombie, zombie,
zombie-ie-ie, oh ♪
♪ Du, du, du, du ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Another mother's breaking ♪
♪ Heart is taking over ♪
♪ When the violence
causes silence ♪
♪ We must be mistaken ♪
♪ It's the same old theme ♪
♪ Since 1916 ♪
♪ In your head, in your head,
they're still fighting ♪
♪ With their tanks,
and their bombs ♪
♪ And their bombs,
and their guns ♪
♪ In your head, in your head,
they are dying ♪
♪ In your head, in your head ♪
♪ Zombie, zombie, zombie-ie-ie ♪
♪ What's in your head,
in your head ♪
♪ Zombie, zombie, zombie-ie-ie ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh, ay, oh, ya ya ♪
♪♪♪
[MUSIC ENDING]